<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MAPP_CA1</string>
    <string name="meetup_name">Meetup Name</string>
    <string name="meetup_description">Meetup Description</string>
    <string name="edit_meet_name">e.g Lets study math!</string>
    <string name="edit_meet_desc">e.g Need help on differentiation and integration for A Math! I can teach English in return</string>
    <string name="meet_up_date">Date of Meetup</string>
    <string name="date_hint">Wed, Apr 25, 2018</string>
    <string name="hint_time">5.30pm-7.30pm</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="send_button_label">send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_termsandconditions">termsandconditions</string>
    <string name="menu_browse">Browse</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="default_info_title">Default Location</string>
    <string name="default_info_snippet">No places found, because location permission is disabled.</string>
    <string name="option_get_place">Get place</string>
    <string name="pick_place">Choose a place</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Current Place Details</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="t_and_c">These FindAStuddy Standard Terms and Conditions written on this application shall manage your use of our application. These Terms will be applied fully and affect to your use of FindAStuddy. By using FindAStuddy, you agreed to accept all terms and conditions written in here. You must not use FindAStuddy if you disagree with any of FindAStuddy Standard Terms and Conditions. Intellectual Property Rights Other than the content you own, under these Terms, FindAStuddy and/or its licensors own all the intellectual property rights and materials contained in FindAStuddy. You are granted limited license only for purposes of viewing the material contained on FindAStuddy. Restrictions You are specifically restricted from all of the following: publishing any FindAStuddy material in any other media; selling, sublicensing and/or otherwise commercializing any FindAStuddy material; publicly performing and/or showing any FindAStuddy material; using this FindAStuddy in any way that is or may be damaging to this FindAStuddy; using this FindAStuddy in any way that impacts user access to this FindAStuddy; using this FindAStuddy contrary to applicable laws and regulations, or in any way may cause harm to the FindAStuddy, or to any person or business entity; engaging in any data mining, data harvesting, data extracting or any other similar activity in relation to this FindAStuddy; using this FindAStuddy to engage in any advertising or marketing. Certain areas of this FindAStuddy are restricted from being access by you and FindAStuddy may further restrict access by you to any areas of this FindAStuddy, at any time, in absolute discretion. Any user ID and password you may have for this FindAStuddy are confidential and you must maintain confidentiality as well. Your Content In these Website Standard Terms and Conditions, \'Your Content\' shall mean any audio, video text, images or other material you choose to display on this FindAStuddy. By displaying Your Content, you grant FindAStuddy a non-exclusive, worldwide irrevocable, sub licensable license to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute it in any and all media. Your Content must be your own and must not be invading any third-party’s rights. FindAStuddy reserves the right to remove any of Your Content from FindAStuddy at any time without notice. No warranties FindAStuddy is provided \'as is,\' with all faults, and FindAStuddy express no representations or warranties, of any kind related to this FindAStuddy or the materials contained on this FindAStuddy. Also, nothing contained on this FindAStuddy shall be interpreted as advising you.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pick_location">Map</string>
    <string name="chatname_example">E.g Chat discussion for science</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chat_details">ChatDetails</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

    <string name="datepicker_name">Material DateTimePicker</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">DateTimePicker Example</string>
    <string name="selected_time">The time you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="selected_date">The date you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="selected_datetime">The date and time you picked will be shown here.</string>
    <string name="pick_time">Pick Time</string>
    <string name="pick_date">Pick Date</string>
    <string name="original_button">Framework Picker</string>
    <string name="pick_datetime">Pick Date+Time</string>
    <string name="mode_24_hours">Use 24 hour mode</string>
    <string name="mode_dark">Use dark theme</string>
    <string name="mode_custom_accent">Use custom accent</string>
    <string name="vibrate">Vibrate on touch</string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss on pause (eg: orientation change)</string>
    <string name="title">Show a title</string>
    <string name="show_version_2">Use marshmallow layout</string>
    <string name="show_year_first">Show the year picker first</string>
    <string name="enable_seconds">Show seconds picker</string>
    <string name="enable_minutes">Show minutes picker</string>
    <string name="limit_times">Limit selectable times</string>
    <string name="limit_dates">Limit selectable dates</string>
    <string name="disable_dates">Disable specific dates</string>
    <string name="disable_times">Disable specific times</string>
    <string name="highlight_dates">Highlight certain dates</string>
    <string name="switch_orientation">Switch scroll orientation</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="tab_title_time">Time</string>
    <string name="tab_title_date">Date</string>
    <string name="tab_title_datetime">Date+Time</string>
</resources>
